

Hoang Bao Vo (Andy)

Date of birth: 19/09/1998 | **Place of birth:** Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | **Nationality:** Vietnamese |

Gender: Male | **Phone number:** (+84) 338705850 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

andy.vo.webdeveloper@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bao-vo-hoang | Github:

https://github.com/andyvo190998 | Portfolio:

https://andyvo190998.github.io/animated-portfolio/

Address: 36 Bờ Bao Tân Thắng, 7600, Hồ Chí Minh, Vietnam (Home)

ABOUT ME

With more than 4 years of experience working in startup and large organizations environments with NextJS, ReactJS, Typescript, NodeJS, Python, REST-APIs, databases such as Postgres, Redis, MongoDB, MySQL, and experience with Microservices Architecture. I am confident to handle most of the tasks related to web applications. I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, hard-working person who can be able to adapt to all challenging situations. I can work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. Please visit my GitHub repositories and portfolio website to see my work to learn more about me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

III SOLARBK - HO CHI MINH, VIETNAM

SOLAR ENERGY ENGINEER - 10/12/2019 - 31/12/2020

Research and find out new technologies that improve the efficiency of solar modules, receive feedback from clients and find the solution to fix that issue on Solar panels.

Ⅲ FULLERTON HEALTH – SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE

WEB DEVELOPERS - 01/07/2021 - 01/10/2021

- Developed, maintained, and enhanced website features using React|S and Node|S.
- Debugged and resolved website issues to ensure optimal functionality and user experience.
- Collaborated with team members to implement new features and improve website performance.

III KIUTRA GMBH - MUNICH, GERMANY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER – 01/04/2023 – CURRENT

- Developed and maintained front-end applications using ReactJS, ensuring seamless user experience and interface responsiveness.
- Designed and implemented APIs using Flask, Quart, and WebSocket, REST API for efficient back-end communication.
- Design and implemented microservices architecture with event-drivent
- Created and managed Python-based middleware to facilitate inter-process communication.
- Provided technical support and set up software applications for the hardware team, ensuring smooth integration between software and hardware components.

Ⅲ JOCHEN SCHWEIZER MYDAYS GROUP – MÜNCHEN, GERMANY

FULLSTACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - 01/12/2024 - CURRENT

- As a passionate Full-Stack Developer, I specialize in building scalable and maintainable web applications using modern technologies. On the frontend, I create intuitive and performant UIs with React and TypeScript, while on the backend, I architect robust solutions using NestJS, PHP, and REST APIs.
- I have a deep understanding of Hexagonal Architecture and Domain-Driven Design (DDD), ensuring that applications are modular, testable, and easy to maintain. - My approach to software development prioritizes clean architecture, scalability, and best practices.
- With experience in microservices and containerized deployments using Docker and Kubernetes, I focus on delivering high-availability and efficient cloud-native solutions. Additionally, I emphasize end-to-end (E2E) testing with in-house developed tools and unit testing, ensuring software reliability and high code quality.

- Driven by innovation and continuous learning, I thrive on solving complex problems and delivering impactful software solutions.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/06/2016 - 01/10/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Ho Chi Minh University Technology and Education

My major is material technology, more specifically, I study about some devices like Transistors, MOSFET, LED, Sensors, TCO,... nanostructure, simulation properties of materials, semiconductors, thin film technology,... deep knowledge of semiconductors and Transistor and General Electronics

Address 1 Vo Van Ngan, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam, 71300, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | Website hcmute.edu.vn |

Field of study Physics, Chemistry, Physical sciences not elsewhere classified | Final grade GPA: 7.64/10 | Thesis Thesis: 9.6/10

01/04/2021 - 01/12/2023 Augsburg, Germany

MASTER OF SCIENCE University of Augsburg

Continues with the subjects of bachelor's degree, I keep digging deeper into Semiconductor Technology, and gain more knowledge of Semiconductor devices (E.g Transistor, Solar cells,...), understand the way it works and how to create it. Beside of that, I am learning the properties of other materials such as Metals, and polymer composites,...

Address Universitätsstraße 2, Augsburg, 86159, Augsburg, Germany | Website www.uni-augsburg.de |

Field of study Chemistry , Physics | Thesis The properties of Cul thin films prepared by spin coating.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **VIETNAMESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

SKILLS

React, Next.js, React Native | typescrypt | Python | Node|S | Angular TS, Angular|S | Microservices Infrastructure

HONOURS AND AWARDS

05/12/2021

Project Manager - Coursera

Those who earn the Google Project Management Certificate have completed six courses, developed by Google, that include hands-on, practice-based assessments and are designed to prepare them for introductory-level roles in Project Management. They are competent in initiating, planning and running both traditional and agile projects.

Link https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/UW5R4PX9ZCVV

28/12/2021

Web developer - Freecodecamp

From this course, i was learning a lot of basic knowledges about javascript and data structure.

Link https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc71b5460b-8133-41f4-94fc-5727c76f5015/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

26/02/2022

web developer - Udemy

This course guides me from front end to back end and including data base like MongoDB.

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-acdd3aa5-ddc5-4778-93b5-c2c5eee59f29.pdf